Hello friends, welcome to you
friends, in today's video I am going to
tell you that a new project has gone live in CHC, I want to
show you the video of ILP 10th, Jhalare, you will
get Rs. 29 for fabric, if the children work on it then
you
can get ₹29 and ₹3 by doing it twice, what work has to be done in it,
what has to be done, I am going to give all the information in today's
video, so let's
start the tree and we will tell you
what you have to do in it and how to
work, which friends
can see here, this promotion,
you have to take out the printout of this pamphlet of difficulty
and you have to take out 15 to 20 printouts
and after taking the printout I want to tell you what
you have to do, as you will
take out the printout, you have to at least
see it here, this video, a photo which
you will be seeing, you have to make 20 to
25 people sit in the same way, that is, you should have
20 to 25 people sitting anywhere, be it
Amla door, courtyard, mango garden,
anywhere, you have to make ten to twenty people  Twenty-five
people have to be seated, and with social distancing,
because right now, due to the record
virus epidemic,
you have to seat them in the same way, keeping in mind the social distancing and social distancing, and all of them,
20 to 25 people. I have told you this,
you have to download it and print it and give it to
those people.
After giving it to them, which you can see here,
you have to keep a laptop
in front of it like this and you will also have to put up a banner. I will
also tell you where to get the banner. You will also be paid for the banner
separately through CST.
You have to show this program to people through it
and you will get 29 rupees.
I want to tell you the name of this program. The
name of the program is Come, People and
Feelings Awareness Program. I will
tell you that in the end, you will get
this work through this solution, how will you get work, through
which you can get 29 rupees,
and I have also got it, which I
am sharing with you people through this video, so that
you can also take this quote leave.
Plus you will be given ₹5 separately for the banner,
so you can see it here, I
want to tell you in full detail, the
name of this program is,
give full details about the details, I am going to give ISPO
Appointed Awareness Program of Delhi,
this program will be conducted, 29
rupees will be given to it, seriously code, you have a new
glass or old one or you must already
know about this program,
listen, this program is conducted only once in a year,
you know, you never know about it sitting above,
so through this video
I am going to give you full information, you
can see
here, in what form it will be given, if
you do
your work in the same way as is being told to you, then only you will get this
money,
this will increase the grace, there are
all the rules for the year, following them from the fruit point of view, you have to
seat 25 people, you have to make
arrangements for sitting, you do the same, be it
in the courtyard or anywhere there is a mango
garden, wherever it is, there should be
seating facility, you will have to seat 25 people there, for this
you will have to sit 18  You should be
between 60 years and let me
tell you that fifty percent means all the
people sitting in Jio and the people coming in it, you have to give
this slip in the hands of all of
them, I had said pin up,
and look in the hands,
I want to tell you that you have to
show a video like you will give it in the hands, so that
you are sitting with a potato holding a laptop,
you have to show this video which should have a
womb behind it,
I want to tell you for this IP program,
in this program
you will have to make a one minute video, that is, you have to
make a one minute video of all the four qualities
and you have to click 10 to 12 photos,
where you have to submit the photos, you have to
submit it there and you will
also be given an excel sheet, what has to be done in the development,
now which will be told in the class,
watch the video till the end, if you whisk, then it is
possible that you will mix up the points which I am telling you, then
you will
not get that 29 rupees even after heating you,
you will be rejected.  Music can be given
friends, with this,
during the program,
you will have to take photos very carefully
that the photos are correct, you will be given money.
As soon as you take photos and video clips,
you have to take clear photos from all four sides.
While taking photos, no one should be
standing or sitting and should
look towards the laptop on one side, should not be here and there.
After that, you will be given
a sloth in that excel sheet,
you have to fill some information about
how it fits. They will
also show you Lightroom.
In this exercise, you have to fill in the details of 45 people, be it a
man or a woman,
you can show this program to anyone, you can
fill in their information with an excel sheet.
What will you have to do for this, like you will have to
fill in their name, you will have to fill in their mobile number, you will have to fill in their
mother's name, you will have to fill in their father's name,
their age will not be complete.
As soon as you provide all the information in a proper
manner, you will be given ₹50, you will be able to get it.
I also want to tell you that
all the people in the photo should be sitting,
whatever photos you click, the
photo in which you take, at that time your side will be
All the people should be seen sitting properly, they should be
sitting and the laptop
should be looking towards the banner, the face in front of you should be
like a loop and should
also be towards the banner and if
anyone is standing and talking to a group or
turning behind the left Robert, then it will
not be possible, you should see him clearly in that way,
I should look at the hands,
look at the pilot who can clip your photo properly,
what is the main objective of this program, this program which is being conducted, a
serial program which
every person is giving on this approach, its
objective is to teach all of them to save,
in that video I will
tell you about Dish in the middle, Kishore, I will also
give its link, which you have to
eat on which you can get this money, so
in this video, the information has been given that
how will you be able to save,
whatever insurance of your family, be it active
RDO, IS, whatever NPS,
you can open such a scheme for the people next to you, for the
people of your family
and how will you be able to save in it, regarding that
This
video has been made. I want to tell you
how you will get this job if you don't talk to me.
What do you have to do to get the job? First of all,
I want to tell you that
in the description box of the video, I will give you a
list of your district managers.
All the district
managers of Bihar have a leg for each district.
You
can get their contact numbers from there. So, first of all, you have to
contact your district manager and
tell them that we want to
participate in the Agri (Investor Awareness Program)
and show them that program. You are a
district manager.
You will be given a link to that link where
you will find all the information. If you click on it,
you will also get an Excel sheet. We will
also show you how it works. Apart from this, stay tuned.
Listen to this video completely. As you can see here, I have a
form given to me. It has been
sent directly to my district manager. I am
thankful to see the benefits of this. So, I want that every person, whether new
or old, can also earn some money
through this program.  It is done only once a
year so that
secondly here this is family, here you have to
give it first and below here
edit your CSC here name here your
mobile number and here you have to give block panchayat
then your merger here and here
you have to give ward number also and after
filling this you have to submit it to the district manager here
as soon as
you submit then you will be given this excel
sheet which you can see, this is how
access is there I will tell you
how to do this program I
want to tell you that you work wisely,
these people burn that at the time when it is going on, if
you also fast correctly then
you can get money twice, you can be given a
total of eight annas by working with friends
and you will be seeing this banner
that I want to show you uncle, you will see this
banner, you will see this divine form of the top, if you want to
print this statement then you will get the
link of the banner in the description box of the video, you
can print it for all the channels there and you will have to get this printer done,
where do you have to put this gallery and
where do you have to put the laptop, this is
told to you here  But you can see it like this,
you are seeing it on the best of, you have to
sit people like this while maintaining social distance, and you have to
keep your laptop on a table and
behind it you have to put a banner of high quality here
and in the same way you have to
click the video, take a video in one go and
you have to click the photo, you have to take eight-ten photos from you,
this is how
you have to program, you must have understood
how to fill the form and how you will get this work,
you have also understood
how you will get the work, then if
I have to do this work of District Race Contrast, then
you will get all the information there and
now the thing is that you can see here,
you have to give this form
to the customer, in which you
will show the photo of the kitchen and here you can
see the link of Bhoga video, video and video
to you, good karz kaise ho sir, you will get to
do both of these, so what you can do is
I will have to show you both the videos, the
video will have to be played there and let me tell you one thing,
you
can do this program very easily here, with scissors  There is
no duality, this payment will be
sent to your wife or CSC wallet,
so the thing is
how will you send your photo, you have
clicked the photo and video in a minute,
send it to your district manager's WhatsApp and tell him that
my program is done, then as soon as he does that, then that
entire data is there, after this
photo and video, the excel which you will be
seeing on others, this letter
is of 45 persons, you will have to clear the correct information of 45 persons here,
like here the salutations are
showing the person, his
mobile number and after that the address, then
father's name, mother's name and SB,
you will have to submit all this complete
information as you feel, then the person to be done has to
WhatsApp this to me, you can
also contact by mail
and you have to give it,
as soon as you send it, there is Joshi manager there, then he will
fry it like a man, he will fry it further
and this money will be
given to you in some accessibility DGP
and you will get your banner money separately
₹500  So friends, the only purpose of making this video was
that whatever
decision I have taken, I want you people to also take
advantage of it, whoever is new or has
got it from the past, everyone should get this benefit
because at present CSC is
bringing many such facilities, if
you do this work then you will be given this work every year and
every time you will be given the renewable
CSP update, that too will be
given to you, so friends, how did you like this video, you
can tell us in the comment box,
if you are reading my channel for the first time, then
please subscribe to the channel and also send
out the bill notification, so that the
upcoming notifications will
reach the officers first and
absolutely free, so friends,
this is a new approach to creating employment for them, Jai Hind Jai
Bharat